{
    "id": "09c356fb2b834d99976e0c147b52d628",
    "title": "Errors In Nouns And Verbs",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Be careful not to .................................. your money.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lose",
                "loose"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "579ae5f2867441efbc10548ab9e33fdb"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have they ................................... this box?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "weighed",
                "weighted"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "daa6c48a086d4f93a500a3ee427aaf23"
        },
        {
            "question": "Mathematics ....................................... not easy to learn.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "24c45207a1cd4a1daf3789a491961573"
        },
        {
            "question": "You have to learn this ...................................... by heart.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "poem",
                "poetry"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e603bdd4029a4d81b869ea5dcbd622f6"
        },
        {
            "question": "When she entered her room, she saw her books lying on the ..............................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "floor",
                "ground"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "208adab67f644ae9aa2358174636ec0a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which is the ............................................. to the railway station?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "road",
                "street"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dd85992dfa7e4bc3a5a74ea4ba5779d9"
        },
        {
            "question": "Are you .......................................... in this program?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "interesting",
                "interested"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "05b89793673e4536b41c3d9766ec50b3"
        },
        {
            "question": "She sometimes ...................................... purple shoes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wears",
                "puts on"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "28cbbabe19ab408e885b3130e2233234"
        },
        {
            "question": "There .................................. a lot of apples on the tree.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3f8947ece9484875b3873874cb246de0"
        },
        {
            "question": "What ........................................... eat?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do cows",
                "cows"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1162b0c14388451eb4f036eba49c90cd"
        }
    ]
}